infosorce.com 2019-03-03

# Privacy Policy

If you require any more information and detail or have any question about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by  _[Contact Us](https://infosorce.com/contact-us/)_.

At Infosorce.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by infosorce.com and how we use it.

This Privacy Statement is designed to provide information about Infosorce privacy and data collection practices. This privacy policy does not apply to Sites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we may link or who may link to us. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third-party websites.

The website address _Https://infosorce.com_ is owned by  _[Naveen Kumar SIngh](https://infosorce.com/about-us/)._ All material on this website is provided for your information only. The information expressed here are believed to be accurate, based on the knowledge gained by author/owner. In addition, the information expressed here do not necessarily reflect the views of the author. Infosorce acknowledges that information given on this website is based on information available on different websites. The publisher is not responsible for errors or omissions.

Email addresses mentioned in the comment form and feedback is totally secure and will always be used for privacy and never be used for spamming or sold to anyone.

We love to comment and feedback, but some comments which are abusive, spread hatred, are racial, or in any way hurting anyone`s opinions will not get approved and we delete such kind of comments. We keep our comments moderated to maintain the integrity of every individual. We reserve all right to accept or reject any comments.

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor`s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized sting created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here:- https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

Like many other Web sites, Infosorce.com makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the sites – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. The information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Infosorce.com uses cookies to store information about visitor’s preference, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses revisits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitor’s browser types or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

→Google, as third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Infosorce.com

→Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to infosorce.com and other sites on the Internet.

→Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web become on our site. Our advertising partners include…..

⇒Google

_While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here:  [Privacy Policies](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/privacy-policies/)._

_You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of infosorce.com_

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on infosorce.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

Infosorce.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Infosorce.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot the activities of, such other advertisers or websites. You may find a comprehensive listing of these privacy policies and their links here: [Privacy Policy Links](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/privacy-policy-links).

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browser’s respective websites.

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. infosorce.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that infosorce.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
